http://www.searchme.com/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
Searchme Site and Services
This Privacy Policy applies to the Searchme Site and Services and is independent of any other site, services, or application(s) you may be installing or
using concurrently. The Searchme Site and Services are provided and maintained by Searchme, which may be referred to herein as "Searchme," "We," "Us," or
"Our" whether in uppercase, lowercase, or a combination.
We want you to know that We care about your privacy and We will never intentionally collect personally identifiable information or monitor usage on an
personally identifiable individual level.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Because of the rapidly evolving nature of the internet, computers, mobile technologies, and other technologies, in Our attempts to make Our user experience
better, and for other aesthetic and business reasons, We may change, update and modify the Privacy Policy from time to time. We will attempt to notify you
about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a notice on Our site at http://searchme.com/
and perhaps more specifically at http://searchme.com/privacy.html or in some other reasonable manner so You may always make yourself aware or be aware
of what has changed. If any modification is unacceptable to You, You shall cease using the Site and Services right away. If You do not cease using the Site
and Services, You will be conclusively deemed to have accepted the change(s). Except as stated elsewhere, any amended Privacy Policy shall automatically be
effective as soon as it is initially posted except if We state that We are giving advance notice of any amended term to be effective on a date in the
future. You agree that it is your responsibility to check the Privacy Policy and any guidelines periodically for changes. Except as posted by Us this
Privacy Policy may not be otherwise amended, and no term may be waived by Us, except in a writing, hand signed by pen on paper (or as set forth below) by
You and an authorized representative of Ours. For purposes of this provision, a "writing" does not include an email message, text, chat, or the like, sent
from any device existing now or later developed and a signature does not include an electronic signature.
Information we collect during Usage of the Site or Services
We do not monitor the web pages you visit. When you perform a search, your search may be sent through Our servers in order to optimize the search result.
This will record the following information:
Date and time of Your visit to our Site
Date and time of Your search
Originating IP address
Media access control ("MAC") and operating system data
Search term(s)
In addition, the browser will communicate to Us information it gives to every web server that has placed one or more active cookies on such browser: ip
address and browser user agent that contains information about the applicable computer or device hardware and software attributes.
How we use the Information we collect
All information collected is reported by us on an aggregate basis. We may use this information to measure, for example:
the total number of Site visits and Service uses
browser type (to study browser trends, for example)
MAC and operating system data
Information collected by Third Parties
Search results pages you visit when performing a search using our Site or Services are provided by Our search engine partners (e.g.,Yahoo, Baidu, Yandex,
eBay, Amazon, Namespace, etc.). These search engines can and might track a variety of data, including the following:
Search term that was entered into the search box
Originating IP address and the user's country or OS language setting
Sponsored listings or other advertisements that you click on
That the search request came from the relevant Site and its associated revenue tag
MAC and operating system data
We suggest that you consider visiting the sites of these search engines to learn their privacy policies and more information about what they collect, as
well as to determine how you may attempt to prevent the collection of such information, or clear such information. Some of these search engines are members
of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI). To opt out of other ad networks or to learn more about network advertising, please visit the
NAI site and Digital Advertising Alliance website. In
addition, some browsers have "do no track" functionalities or setting, which you might consider learning about.
No Spyware
We do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information or monitor your surfing behavior.
No Adware
The Site does not launch pop-up or pop-under advertisements, or any other obtrusive forms of advertising.
Use of Cookie
s, Pixels, and Web Beacons
When you conduct a search using the Site, Our content providers who supply search results (e.g., Yahoo, Baidu, Yandex, etc.) may set or access cookies on
the computer or device where the search is performed from. The cookies are typically used for the purpose of measuring referrals from Our Site on an
aggregate basis and are not tied to your personal information, except for your IP Address, and usually as may be otherwise disclosed in the privacy
policies of these providers. Many browsers offer users the option of declining or deleting cookies. If you do not wish to accept cookies, or you wish to
delete cookies, please modify the settings in your browser. (A cookie is message given to a web browser by a web server. The message is then sent back to
the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. There are many resources available on the internet that explain in greater detail what
cookies are, what types of cookies exist, and what they do.) We may also use small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters called cookies
to improve overall Site experience, among other things. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive or browser containing information about
the user. Information from cookies alone generally do not provide us with information to personally identify You. We may use both session cookies and
persistent cookies. A session cookie generally disappears after You close Your browser. A persistent cookie remains after You close Your browser and may be
used by Your browser on subsequent visits to a Searchme Site or other web sites. Persistent cookies can generally be removed by You. Please review Your web
browser "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify Your cookie settings and to remove cookies. We may also use pixels or web beacons on our Site. (See,
e.g.,http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_beacons.)
Also, please refer to the section above titled "Information collected by Third Parties"
Children's Privacy
We recognize the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and
interests. The Site and Services are not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not target the Site or our Services to children under 13. We do
not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS
THE SITE OR SERVICES AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. IF WE LEARN THAT PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION OF PERSONS YOUNGER THAN 13 YEARS OF AGE HAS BEEN
COLLECTED ON OR THROUGH OUR A SITE, WE WILL TAKE THE APPROPRIATE STEPS TO DELETE THIS INFORMATION.
IF YOU ARE THE PARENT OR LEGAL GUARDIAN OF A CHILD YOUNGER THAN 13 YEARS OF AGE WHO HAS BECOME AN SITE USER SUBSCRIBER, THEN PLEASE CONTACT US AT
INFO_at_SEARCHME_dot_COM TO HAVE THAT CHILD'S ACCOUNT TERMINATED AND INFORMATION DELETED.
THE FOLLOWING ARE SOME RESOURCES THAT MAY HELP PARENTS AND LEGAL GUARDIANS IN MONITORING AND LIMITING THEIR CHILDREN'S ACCESS TO CERTAIN TYPES OF MATERIAL
ON THE INTERNET. WHILE WE DO NO ENDORSE THESE SITES, SERVICES, OR PRODUCTS, AND DISCLAIM ANY RESPONSIBILITY IN CONNECTION WITH THEM, WE PROVIDE INFORMATION
ABOUT THEM AS A PUBLIC SERVICE.
OnGuard Online
, maintained by the Federal Trade Commission.
WiredSafety
Netsmartz.org
The Child Safety Network
Control Kids
Cyber Sitter
Net Nanny
INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE
We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've
requested, when We have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
We provide the information to trusted business affiliates who work with Us or on Our behalf under confidentiality agreements. These companies may
use your personal information to help Us communicate with you about offers from Us and Our marketing partners.
We have a parent's permission to share the information if the user is a child under age 13. Parents have the option of allowing Us to collect and
use their child's information without consenting to Our sharing of this information with people and companies who may use this information for
their own purposes.
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, and We may provide information and data pursuant to same, and We may use you information
and date to establish or exercise Our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities, fraud,
situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Our Terms http://searchme.com/terms.html,
or as may otherwise be required by law or regulation.
We transfer information about you if We are acquired by or merged with another company.
Notice to European Users
The information You enter on or through a Site or Service or otherwise provide to Us may be transferred outside of the European Union to the United States
of America, which does not offer an equivalent level of protection to that required in the European Union. In particular, You are advised that the United
States of America uses a sectoral model of privacy protection that relies on a mix of legislation, governmental regulation, and self-regulation. Article 26
of the European Union's Data Protection Directive (Directive 95/46/EC, 1995 O.J. (L 281) 31) allows for transfer of personal data from the European Union
to a third country if the individual has unambiguously given his consent to the transfer of personal information, regardless of the third country's level
of protection. By agreeing to the Terms http://searchme.com/terms.html and this Privacy Policy, You consent to the
transfer of all such information to the United States of America, which may not offer an equivalent level of protection to that required in the European
Union and to the processing of that information by Us on our servers located in the United States of America as described in this Privacy Policy.
Questions and Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please send us a note at
.
Effective Date: March 21, 2013
